ilrg.com 2015-09-06

# ILRG.com: Terms and Conditions of Use

#### 

_WE RESPECT YOUR PRIVACY_

Last Updated: June 23, 2015 

**NOTICE:[Click here](http://www.consumer.ftc.gov/) for important information about safe surfing from the Federal Trade Commission. **

[Maximilian Ventures LLC](http://www.maximilian.net/), a Delaware limited liability company doing business as "PublicLegal" and "PublicLegalForms.com", owns and operates the Internet Legal Research Group website, www.ilrg.com (hereafter, the "Site" or "ILRG.com.") Maximilian Ventures LLC promotes trust, privacy and security as core attributes of our service to our user. Maximilian Ventures LLC has adopted this Privacy Policy ("Policy") to communicate clearly our firm commitment to your privacy. It is this respect for user privacy that is a fundamental component to our mission. Using our website demonstrates your consent to Maximilian Ventures LLC's collection and use of information pursuant to this Policy, and continued use of this site following the posting of changes to this Policy will signify your acceptance of such changes. This Policy governs the use of your name, e-mail address, payment information, and similar personal information that you may provide us in the course of using our website, products or services. 

[Maximilian Ventures LLC](http://www.maximilian.net/) has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy statement and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal. TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, http://www.ilrg.com. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. 

**Information Collection and Use.** Maximilian Ventures LLC collects personal information to provide certain products and services to our customers. For example, if you: 

  * Place a product or service order, Maximilian Ventures LLC will receive your name, e-mail address, and credit card information only for the purpose of fulfilling your order and charging you for the product or service you have ordered. We encrypt your information using industry-leading encryption technology. We do not retain or store credit your card information, except for the last four digits of your credit card number, which we retain only for the purpose of authenticating you in case you contact us later for help or support with your order.
  * Request promotional items, Maximilian Ventures LLC will collect and use your name and address, or e-mail address;
  * Post information on any of our interactive areas, Maximilian Ventures LLC will collect information from you in order to e-mail you major updates about Internet Legal Research Group, the products and services;
  * Sign-up for the Internet Legal Research Group mailing list, Maximilian Ventures LLC will collect information from you to facilitate the publishing of that mailing list; and
  * Send our link to others through our website, Maximilian Ventures LLC will collect the information from you only for the purpose of facilitating the transmission of the e-mail. We will send this email only and no following promotional emails unless the recipient specifically chooses to receive future promotional emails from us.

Information that you submit about yourself may be used by Maximilian Ventures LLC to provide you requested services, communicate with you about our products, improve your online experience, or support our continuing efforts to offer you the information and services you want most. We do not share personal information about you with non-affiliated companies or organizations outside of Maximilian Ventures LLC without your explicit permission. Maximilian Ventures LLC does, however, provide aggregate statistics and information about our sales, traffic patterns and related site information to third parties. 

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. If Maximilian Ventures LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

**Confidentiality and Security.** Maximilian Ventures LLC limits access to personal information about you to employees and contractors who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. Maximilian Ventures LLC has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. In addition, as a condition of employment or business partnership, Maximilian Ventures LLC requires all its employees and contractors to sign confidentiality contracts. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us by emailing [webmaster03@ilrg.com](mailto:webmaster03@ilrg.com). 

**Maximilian Ventures LLC's Security is Certified Daily by an Independent Third Party.** Maximilian Ventures LLC has contracted with [McAfee, Inc.](http://www.mcafeesecure.com/) (NYSE: [MFE](http://www.google.com/finance?q=MFE)), the leading provider of Internet security auditing services, to provide independent daily monitoring, testing, and certification of Maximilian Ventures LLC's web site and e-commerce security. Maximilian Ventures LLC is tested and certified daily to pass the FBI/SANS Internet Security Test. The "live" McAfee® Secure mark, shown on the right, appears only when a web site's security meets the highest security scanning standards of the U.S. government, Visa, MasterCard, American Express, Discover, and JCB. The daily scanning and certification show that Maximilian Ventures LLC meets all payment card industry guidelines for remote web server vulnerability testing to help protect customer personal information from hackers. McAfee SECURE sites help keep you safe from identity theft, credit card fraud, spyware, spam, viruses and online scams. 

**Security with Symantec® and SSL.** Maximilian Ventures LLC has contracted with [Symantec Corporation](http://www.symantec.com/). (NASDAQ: [SYMC](http://www.google.com/finance?q=SYMC)), the leading provider of digital authentication services and products for electronic commerce and other forms of secure communications. With Symantec, you are assured that you have secure communications with Maximilian Ventures LLC and not another site. Maximilian Ventures LLC uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer), the industry standard method for computers to communicate securely without risk of manipulation or recipient impersonation. Maximilian Ventures LLC utilizes this encryption during the online checkout process, including the acceptance of your credit card information, and the management of your account. The "Norton Secured" Symantec mark, shown on the right, appears only when a business has passed Symantec's rigorous identity authentication process and has been certified as a valid and trusted business. 

**E-mail Announcements and Newsletters.** Maximilian Ventures LLC occasionally uses e-mail to send announcements regarding new products, services, and/or promotions, and informational newsletters that would be of interest to our customers. Announcements via email are on an opt-in basis only. By posting material on any of our interactive areas, you are opting in to receiving these e-mail announcements. You can choose to unsubscribe to Maximilian Ventures LLC e-mail at any time by visiting <https://www.ilrg.com/updates>. Maximilian Ventures LLC will also send replies to customer e-mail via e-mail. Finally, if you have sent a request to Maximilian Ventures LLC about which we need to communicate with you, we may do so by e-mail or telephone, if you provided your telephone number to us. 

**Updating Your Information.** As a customer of Maximilian Ventures LLC, or as a subscriber to one of our opt-in email lists or newsletters, you may alter or delete your information or opt-out of receiving communications from us at any time. Maximilian Ventures LLC offers the following options for changing and modifying your information. 

  1. You may send an email to [webmaster03@ilrg.com](mailto:webmaster03@ilrg.com). 
  2. You may send mail to Maximilian Ventures LLC at the following postal address: 2711 Centerville Road, Suite 120-5800, Wilmington, Delaware 19808 USA
  3. You may call us at: +1 (800) 987-9087, ext. 2
  4. You may fax us at +1 (815) 572-5766
  5. Or, for newsletters and email lists only, you may unsubscribe at the following URL: <https://www.ilrg.com/updates>. 

We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. 

**Anti-Spam Policy.** Maximilian Ventures LLC is 100% opposed to unsolicited commercial email ("spam"). Maximilian Ventures LLC does not send emails to anyone without permission and does not sell or provide email addresses to any unauthorized third party. If you receive any unsolicited emails from spammers, please be assured that Maximilian Ventures LLC did not provide your email address to such parties. 

**Log Files.** As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you. 

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Maximilian Ventures LLC and our marketing and advertising partners, affiliates, or analytics or online customer support providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users’ settings (e.g. for authentication). Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. 

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. 

Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. 

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

**Advertisement Partnership.** Maximilian Ventures LLC maintains a relationship with [TribalFusion](http://www.tribalfusion.com/), Inc., a third-party advertisement and brokerage firm, for the purpose of displaying advertisements to visitors of the Site. While we use cookies in other parts of Maximilian Ventures LLC, cookies received with banner advertisements displayed on the Site are collected by TribalFusion, and we have no access to or control over these cookies. This Policy covers the use of cookies by Maximilian Ventures LLC only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. In the course of serving advertisements, TribalFusion may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites to provide advertisements on the Site and other sites about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp) web site. In addition, you may wish to read [TribalFusion's Privacy Policy](http://www.tribalfusion.com/TribalFusion/privacy.html). 

**Interactive Areas.** Maximilian Ventures LLC is not liable for information posted in interactive areas. Maximilian Ventures LLC provides interactive areas such as polling forums to enhance the user experience and to build a healthy community around our website's products and services. You acknowledge that should you participate in such interactive areas, the information you voluntarily post about yourself and third parties in such areas might be accessed, collected and used by third parties outside of the Site. In addition, you may not post any defamatory, obscene, slanderous, or otherwise illegal material, or any material which infringes any third-party copyrights or other intellectual property rights on any interactive areas. Violators will be subject to termination of accounts and possible legal action. Although Maximilian Ventures LLC employs advanced security technology, it cannot guarantee complete security in personal websites or password-protected areas, and Maximilian Ventures LLC will not be held liable for any user's or other visitor's disclosure of personal information on the Site or any other website operated by Maximilian Ventures LLC. If you are under 18 years of age, you should ask your parents permission before posting any personal information on the Internet, such as your name, address, age, or e-mail address. 

**Data Retention.** We are committed to following the highest standards and best practices within the industry for privacy and security as it relates to data retention. Consistent with those standards, under no circumstances do we ever retain or store your credit card information. The only exception is that we will retain only the last four digits of your credit card number, which, as noted above, we will retain only for the purpose of authenticating you in case you contact us later for help or support. We will retain your information (such as name and/or email address) for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, email us at [webmaster03@ilrg.com](mailto:webmaster03@ilrg.com), or call us on +1 (800) 987-9087, ext. 2, or contact us by one of the other methods noted above. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

**Service Provider.** Maximilian Ventures LLC uses a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personal information for any secondary purposes. 

**Links to External Sites.** Maximilian Ventures LLC contains thousands of links to websites not owned or controlled by Maximilian Ventures LLC. Maximilian Ventures LLC is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any such sites. Our Privacy Policy is a component of, and incorporated into, our [Terms and Conditions of Use](https://www.ilrg.com/terms). This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Maximilian Ventures LLC. 

**Surveys and Contests.** From time-to-time Maximilian Ventures LLC requests information from our visitors via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is voluntary, and the visitor therefore has a choice whether to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and mailing address, as well as demographic information (such as zip code or age). Contact information is used to notify the winners and to award prizes. Survey information is used for purposes improving the use and satisfaction of this site, as well as the relevance of our product offerings and content. 

**Notification of Changes.** Maximilian Ventures LLC will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. If we make any material changes in our privacy practices, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users prior to the change becoming effective. In some cases where we post the notice, we also email users, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. You are responsible for checking this policy periodically to monitor any changes to our privacy practices. Maximilian Ventures LLC reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. 

**A Special Note about Children.** Children are not eligible to use our services, and Maximilian Ventures LLC asks that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to Maximilian Ventures LLC. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with your parents or guardians. 

**Contacting the Web Site.** If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: [Maximilian Ventures LLC](http://www.maximilian.net/), 2711 Centerville Road, Suite 120-5800, Wilmington, Delaware 19808, United States of America; +1 (800) 987-9087 or +1 (815) 572-5766 (fax); or [webmaster03@ilrg.com](mailto:webmaster03@ilrg.com).
